Ever since we...
You're the only person
that I've ever...
Sorry, this is weird.
I-I don't talk like this.
No, it's okay.
I feel like I'm coming apart.
I think about you
all the time, Nikki.
I try not to...
...you're in every song
I listen to.
You were the only person
who was nice to me
when I moved here.
And at first,
I thought maybe you...
Well, I realized who you are.
And then, after Nana passed,
you were the one that called
even when I didn't have
anything to say
and we just sat there.
So I keep telling myself,
"Don't tell her.
"She's too good.
And she'll... you'll lose her."
But maybe you should know...
...that I would choose you
over everything.
Aw.
-That's everything.
-No, no. Stop.
-Okay, th-th-that was cringey.
-Oh, my God. I knew it.
-Way too much.
-I-I'm so sorry.
I thought that was sweet.
-I thought it was gross.
-I-I should've...
-Okay, this time I want you...
-No, I...
I'm not doing it again, dude.
-That was so embarrassing.
-Yeah, yeah.
That would freak...
Th-Th-That freaked me out.
Okay? Nikki would vomit.
You told me to pour
my heart out.
Do you know how vulnerable
I just got?
I underestimated you.
-What if you got her
something nice? -No, no.
-I'll try that.
-D-Don't get her anything.
Dude, you got to be less...
way less sappy with Nikki, okay?
She doesn't like that shit.
She doesn't.
Flowers, the candy
that she said she likes?
Okay.
Thank you.
What?
You want me to go?
-Yeah, if-if you want, yeah.
-Oh, yeah, okay. Yeah.
I'm sorry that...
I'm sorry I made you do that.
No. No, it's okay. You're okay.
-No, it-it just...
-It's a fun break.
-Just pretend like...
-You're good.
Oh, my God, dude,
that was so embarrassing.
Can we leave?
Yeah, well, thank God I did it.
That was... that was awful.
Thank you for that.
Have you ever actually, like,
flirted with Nikki?
Invite romance.
-Invite romance?
-Tease her.
-Be playfully mean with her.
-Be mean to her?
Playfully mean, yeah,
but bring up Freaky Nikki.
You want me to call her
Freaky Nikki?
You know she's sensitive
about that.
Be like, "Hey, remember when
you used to get bullied?
Everybody called you
Freaky Nikki?"
She'll be like, "Oh, my God.
"Oh, no, Bear, that was...
that was so long ago.
Don't. Please."
And that will, like,
take her breath away?
Just say,
"Nikki, I think we should grab
a drink sometime."
Yeah, I've grabbed drinks
sometimes.
She always invites you.
-Yeah, exactly.
-I asked you guys not to come
to trivia for one night.
Y-You can't ask her out
at trivia, Bear.
You can't.
I-I'm not gonna let you.
It's a good,
organic time to ask.
I love trivia night.
It's all I have.
I wake up every Wednesday
rock hard,
thinking about trivia.
God, I can't get over
how dumb I just looked.
Y-You can't turn
our weekly gathering
of camaraderie and skill
i-into your... your...
your seven-year-late
promposal, Bear.
Then when do I ask?
Any other time.
All you have is time.
If she means this much to you--
and I know she does-- wait.
Do it at the right time.
Okay.
Okay, I'll wait.
-I'll do it right.
-Now say it with me.
All you have is time.
Oh, no.
Sandy?
No.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no. No, no!
Oh, shit.
How did you get into these?
Oh, man.